The Diary of Ellen Rimbauer is a drama, horror,
mystery film directed by Craig R. Baxley.
Set at the turn of the century, this is the tale of Ellen Rimbauer who just received
this mysterious mansion as a wedding gift from her new husband...
Ellen Gilcrest Rimbauer, played by Lisa Brenner.
John Rimbauer, played by Steven Brand.
Connie Posey, played by Kate Burton.
Sukeena, played by Tsidii Leloka.
Doug Posey, played by Brad Greenquist.
Fanny, played by Deirdre Quinn.
The Diary of Ellen Rimbauer is a 2003 American
television film directed by Craig R.
Baxley, and starring Lisa Brenner, Steven Brand, and Tsidii Le Loka.
It is a prequel to the miniseries Rose Red (2002), and is based on the 2001 novel by
Ridley Pearson, which itself is an accompaniment piece to the miniseries.
The film premiered on ABC on May 12, 2003.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, medium, haunted house.
The tone is dark and intense and emotional.